thank you very much ladies and gentlemen
thank you down and cue Debbie but this
evening it's not about me it's about
this amazing lady here sitting on my
mind right and I'm very honored that I
could be asked to induct mrs. who genius
the hardship to the Cleveland
international Hall of Fame she is one of
our most accomplished polish Americans
the main reason why we honor her this
evening and we're here from the official
induction is her radio programs she has
been broadcasting on the airwaves for of
the normal 55 years 61 just four years
after her arrival in cleveland oh jen
has allowed shipping on her radio career
working together with her late husband
Hessian after his passing in 1983 she
continued to make progress by herself
during her long and distinguished
broadcasting career she has interviewed
hundreds of outstanding polish artists
and scholars along with raising three
daughters one of whom I've had the
pleasure to meet this evening she has
devoted herself to the authorization of
Polish culture and continues to do so
until this very day since 1988 a result
as a result of the diligent efforts she
is also produced
program on public radio wcp n 90.3 FM
promoting polish classical music article
train interviews with distinguished
guests she continues her work on both
stations serving the Polish American
community Oh genetics great great pride
and is recognized for continuing the two
oldest polish radio programs in America
founded back in 1927 she wasn't around
back then yes she's very open to the
changing media world and our programs
are also available stream to the
Internet beside her radio Karina she's
also a local correspondent for the
chicago-based daily genitals quarter
she's organized numerous concerts
exhibitions lectures plays and has made
many appearances on the global
television promoting Polish culture and
traditions she has co-ordinated many
events with the ethnic heritage silages
Studies program at Cleveland State
University she's a member of numerous
polish-american organizations and for
porn her achievements we too have
recognized and honored her for the
government of the republic of poland has
awarded her with the order of merit she
is a role model for Polish Americans she
has devoted her life to the Polish
community but also and primarily to
community in Cleveland her voice is
respected and her programs remain of
popular and relevant working since
for 55 years in a single professional
field is an achievement in itself mrs.
Florrick did not only that she has kept
unpublished presence in the highly
competitive world of mass media and is
still after those 55 years going strong
please accept my heartfelt
congratulations we are
you